<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project_plan>
    <node title="Mac-Specific Implementation Strategy" priority="high" status="pending" id="mac-implementation-module-001">
        <comment>Focused implementation plan for Mac platform targeting direct competition with MacWhisper. Emphasizes native Mac integration, performance optimization, and user experience patterns that Mac users expect from professional applications.</comment>
        
        <node title="Native Mac Integration Foundation" priority="high" status="pending" id="mac-integration-foundation-002">
            <comment>Implement deep Mac system integration that makes VoiceFlow feel like a native Mac application rather than a cross-platform port. These features create switching costs and user loyalty.</comment>
            
            <node title="macOS System Framework Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="macos-framework-integration-003">
                <comment>Leverage native macOS frameworks for superior performance and integration. Use Core Audio for better audio handling, AVFoundation for media processing, and Metal Performance Shaders for GPU acceleration.</comment>
                
                <node title="Core Audio Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="core-audio-integration-004">
                    <comment>Implement native Core Audio APIs for superior audio input/output handling. This provides better microphone access, lower latency for real-time transcription, and automatic audio device switching that matches system preferences.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Metal Performance Shaders GPU Acceleration" priority="high" status="pending" id="metal-gpu-acceleration-005">
                    <comment>Utilize Metal Performance Shaders for Whisper model inference on Apple Silicon. This provides significant speed advantages over generic GPU computing approaches and matches MacWhisper's performance claims.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="AVFoundation Media Processing" priority="medium" status="pending" id="avfoundation-processing-006">
                    <comment>Use AVFoundation for robust media file handling and format conversion. This provides better compatibility with macOS audio/video formats and automatic metadata extraction.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="macOS UI/UX Native Patterns" priority="high" status="pending" id="macos-ui-patterns-007">
                <comment>Implement macOS-specific UI patterns that make the application feel authentically native. Mac users have strong expectations for interface consistency with system conventions.</comment>
                
                <node title="Native macOS Menu Bar Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="native-menu-bar-008">
                    <comment>Implement comprehensive menu bar with standard macOS menu organization: File, Edit, View, Tools, Window, Help. Include standard keyboard shortcuts (Cmd+O, Cmd+S, Cmd+W) that Mac users expect for file operations.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="macOS Toolbar &amp; Touch Bar Support" priority="medium" status="pending" id="toolbar-touchbar-009">
                    <comment>Design native macOS toolbar with customizable buttons for frequent actions. Include Touch Bar support for MacBook Pro users with contextual controls during transcription and editing processes.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Native macOS Dialog &amp; Sheet Patterns" priority="medium" status="pending" id="native-dialog-patterns-010">
                    <comment>Use native NSOpenPanel, NSSavePanel, and sheet-style dialogs that slide down from the title bar. Mac users expect specific dialog behaviors and button ordering (Cancel/OK rather than OK/Cancel).</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="macOS Dark Mode &amp; Accent Color Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="dark-mode-accent-011">
                    <comment>Implement automatic dark/light mode switching based on system preferences. Use system accent colors and vibrancy effects where appropriate to match user's personalized macOS appearance.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="File System &amp; Workflow Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="file-system-integration-012">
                <comment>Deep integration with macOS file system and user workflows that creates convenience and switching costs. These integrations make VoiceFlow part of the user's daily Mac workflow.</comment>
                
                <node title="Finder Integration &amp; Quick Actions" priority="high" status="pending" id="finder-integration-013">
                    <comment>Register file type associations for common audio formats and add Finder Quick Actions for right-click transcription. Users should be able to right-click any audio file in Finder and select "Transcribe with VoiceFlow".</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Spotlight Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="spotlight-integration-014">
                    <comment>Make transcripts searchable through Spotlight by implementing proper metadata indexing. Users should be able to find transcripts by searching for content within them from Spotlight search.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Services Menu Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="services-menu-015">
                    <comment>Add VoiceFlow services to the macOS Services menu for transcribing selected audio files from any application. This provides system-wide access to transcription functionality.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="iCloud Drive Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="icloud-drive-integration-016">
                    <comment>Integrate with iCloud Drive for automatic transcript backup and cross-device sync. This provides seamless access to transcripts across Mac, iPhone, and iPad without requiring separate cloud service signup.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Performance Optimization for Mac" priority="high" status="pending" id="performance-optimization-mac-017">
            <comment>Optimize performance specifically for Mac hardware characteristics, especially Apple Silicon. Performance advantages create compelling reasons to choose VoiceFlow over competitors.</comment>
            
            <node title="Apple Silicon Optimization" priority="high" status="pending" id="apple-silicon-optimization-018">
                <comment>Leverage unique capabilities of Apple Silicon M-series chips for superior transcription performance. This includes Neural Engine utilization and unified memory architecture advantages.</comment>
                
                <node title="Neural Engine Acceleration" priority="high" status="pending" id="neural-engine-acceleration-019">
                    <comment>Investigate and implement Neural Engine acceleration for Whisper model inference. This could provide significant speed advantages over GPU-only approaches, especially for real-time transcription.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Unified Memory Architecture Optimization" priority="medium" status="pending" id="unified-memory-optimization-020">
                    <comment>Optimize memory usage patterns for Apple Silicon's unified memory architecture. This allows larger models to run efficiently and enables better multitasking during transcription.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Energy Efficiency Optimization" priority="medium" status="pending" id="energy-efficiency-021">
                    <comment>Optimize for macOS energy efficiency to maintain performance during battery operation. Include low-power mode that adjusts transcription quality/speed based on battery level and power source.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Intel Mac Compatibility" priority="medium" status="pending" id="intel-mac-compatibility-022">
                <comment>Ensure optimal performance on Intel-based Macs while prioritizing Apple Silicon. Many professional users still use Intel Macs and represent significant market opportunity.</comment>
                
                <node title="Intel GPU Acceleration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="intel-gpu-acceleration-023">
                    <comment>Implement GPU acceleration for Intel integrated and discrete graphics. This ensures competitive performance on Intel Macs compared to MacWhisper and other competitors.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Rosetta 2 Performance Testing" priority="medium" status="pending" id="rosetta-performance-testing-024">
                    <comment>Test and optimize performance when running on Apple Silicon under Rosetta 2 translation. Ensure graceful fallback performance if native Apple Silicon builds encounter issues.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Mac-Specific Feature Implementation" priority="high" status="pending" id="mac-specific-features-025">
            <comment>Implement features that leverage unique Mac capabilities and address specific Mac user workflows. These features differentiate VoiceFlow from cross-platform competitors.</comment>
            
            <node title="System Audio Capture" priority="high" status="pending" id="system-audio-capture-026">
                <comment>Implement system audio capture for transcribing Zoom meetings, online courses, and system playback. This is a key feature that MacWhisper offers and users frequently request.</comment>
                
                <node title="Audio Hijack Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="audio-hijack-integration-027">
                    <comment>Integrate with or replicate Audio Hijack functionality for capturing audio from specific applications. Allow users to transcribe Zoom meetings, Spotify podcasts, or YouTube videos directly.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Screen Recording Audio Extraction" priority="medium" status="pending" id="screen-recording-audio-028">
                    <comment>Enable extracting audio from QuickTime screen recordings and transcribing them. This supports common workflow of recording meetings/presentations and later transcribing them.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Siri Shortcuts &amp; Automation Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="siri-shortcuts-automation-029">
                <comment>Create Siri Shortcuts for common transcription tasks and integrate with macOS automation tools. This enables voice-activated transcription and workflow automation.</comment>
                
                <node title="Voice Command Transcription" priority="medium" status="pending" id="voice-command-transcription-030">
                    <comment>Implement Siri Shortcuts for "Hey Siri, transcribe my last recording" or "Hey Siri, start transcribing". This provides hands-free operation for accessibility and convenience.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Automator Workflow Actions" priority="low" status="pending" id="automator-workflow-actions-031">
                    <comment>Create Automator actions for batch transcription workflows. Power users can create custom automation for processing multiple files with specific settings and export formats.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Mac Ecosystem Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="mac-ecosystem-integration-032">
                <comment>Integrate with other Mac applications and services that users commonly use in transcription workflows. This creates workflow stickiness and user convenience.</comment>
                
                <node title="Apple Notes Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="apple-notes-integration-033">
                    <comment>Enable direct export to Apple Notes with proper formatting and timestamp linking. Many users want to append transcripts to existing meeting notes or project documentation.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Calendar Event Integration" priority="low" status="pending" id="calendar-integration-034">
                    <comment>Integrate with Calendar.app to automatically name transcripts based on concurrent calendar events. If user transcribes during "Team Meeting", suggest "Team Meeting - [Date]" as transcript title.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Contacts Integration" priority="low" status="pending" id="contacts-integration-035">
                    <comment>Use Contacts.app for speaker identification in multi-person recordings. If user has contact information, attempt to identify speakers by voice characteristics or manual tagging.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Mac App Store &amp; Distribution Strategy" priority="medium" status="pending" id="mac-app-store-distribution-036">
            <comment>Prepare for Mac App Store submission and alternative distribution channels. Mac App Store provides legitimacy and discovery but has restrictions. Direct distribution offers more flexibility.</comment>
            
            <node title="Mac App Store Compliance" priority="medium" status="pending" id="app-store-compliance-037">
                <comment>Ensure compliance with Mac App Store guidelines including sandboxing, entitlements, and privacy requirements. This may restrict some system integration features but provides legitimacy and easier discovery.</comment>
                
                <node title="Sandboxing Strategy" priority="medium" status="pending" id="sandboxing-strategy-038">
                    <comment>Implement App Sandbox compatibility while maintaining key functionality. Some features like system audio capture may require special entitlements or alternative implementations for App Store version.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Privacy Policy &amp; Data Handling" priority="medium" status="pending" id="privacy-policy-data-039">
                    <comment>Develop comprehensive privacy policy emphasizing local processing and minimal data collection. Mac users are increasingly privacy-conscious, and offline processing is a key selling point.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Direct Distribution Option" priority="medium" status="pending" id="direct-distribution-040">
                <comment>Prepare direct distribution infrastructure for users who want features that App Store restrictions prevent. This includes automatic updates, license verification, and download delivery.</comment>
                
                <node title="Notarization &amp; Code Signing" priority="medium" status="pending" id="notarization-code-signing-041">
                    <comment>Implement proper code signing and Apple notarization for direct distribution. This prevents macOS Gatekeeper warnings and provides user confidence in software authenticity.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Direct License Management" priority="medium" status="pending" id="direct-license-management-042">
                    <comment>Implement license key system for direct sales that doesn't require constant internet connectivity. Offline-first design extends to license verification to maintain functionality without network access.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
    </node>
</project_plan>