<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<project_plan>
    <node title="Supabase Integration Strategy" priority="high" status="pending" id="supabase-integration-module-001">
        <comment>Strategic integration of Supabase for desktop-first VoiceFlow application. This approach balances offline-first functionality with cloud-enhanced features, user accounts, and payment processing while maintaining the core value proposition of local processing.</comment>
        
        <node title="Desktop-First + Cloud-Enhanced Architecture" priority="high" status="pending" id="desktop-cloud-architecture-002">
            <comment>Design architecture that prioritizes local functionality while leveraging Supabase for value-added cloud services. The application must work perfectly offline, with cloud services enhancing rather than enabling core functionality.</comment>
            
            <node title="Offline-First Design Principles" priority="high" status="pending" id="offline-first-principles-003">
                <comment>Establish architectural patterns that ensure core transcription functionality works without internet connectivity. Cloud services should be additive features, not dependencies for basic operation.</comment>
                
                <node title="Local Storage Architecture" priority="high" status="pending" id="local-storage-architecture-004">
                    <comment>Implement robust local storage system using SQLite for transcript metadata, file references, and user preferences. Design schema that can sync with Supabase when connectivity is available but functions independently offline.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Offline Transcription Processing" priority="high" status="pending" id="offline-transcription-processing-005">
                    <comment>Ensure all core transcription features (file processing, editing, export) work completely offline. Cloud integration should never block core functionality. This is a key competitive advantage over web-based solutions.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Graceful Cloud Service Degradation" priority="medium" status="pending" id="graceful-cloud-degradation-006">
                    <comment>Design cloud-dependent features to degrade gracefully when offline or when Supabase is unavailable. Show clear status indicators and provide offline alternatives where possible.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Data Sync Strategy &amp; Conflict Resolution" priority="high" status="pending" id="data-sync-strategy-007">
                <comment>Implement intelligent data synchronization that handles conflicts, partial syncs, and maintains data integrity across devices. This is crucial for users working across multiple devices.</comment>
                
                <node title="Transcript Metadata Sync" priority="high" status="pending" id="transcript-metadata-sync-008">
                    <comment>Sync transcript metadata (titles, tags, creation dates, export history) through Supabase while keeping audio files and full transcript content local by default. This provides cross-device access to transcript library without heavy bandwidth usage.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Conflict Resolution Strategy" priority="high" status="pending" id="conflict-resolution-strategy-009">
                    <comment>Implement last-write-wins with manual conflict resolution for transcript edits. When same transcript is edited on multiple devices, present diff view and let user choose resolution. This prevents data loss while maintaining sync functionality.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Selective Cloud Backup" priority="medium" status="pending" id="selective-cloud-backup-010">
                    <comment>Allow users to choose which transcripts to backup to Supabase storage. Implement intelligent suggestions (important transcripts, recent work) while respecting storage quotas and privacy preferences.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="User Account &amp; Authentication Strategy" priority="high" status="pending" id="user-account-auth-strategy-011">
            <comment>Implement user authentication system that enables cloud features and licensing while maintaining privacy and not blocking core functionality. Authentication should enhance the experience without creating barriers.</comment>
            
            <node title="Authentication Implementation" priority="high" status="pending" id="authentication-implementation-012">
                <comment>Set up Supabase Auth with multiple authentication methods optimized for desktop application usage patterns and user preferences.</comment>
                
                <node title="Email/Password Authentication" priority="high" status="pending" id="email-password-auth-013">
                    <comment>Implement standard email/password authentication through Supabase Auth. Include password reset, email verification, and secure session management. This is the foundational authentication method for most users.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Social Authentication Options" priority="medium" status="pending" id="social-auth-options-014">
                    <comment>Add Google and Apple Sign-In options for faster onboarding. Mac users often prefer Apple Sign-In for privacy, while Google provides broader accessibility. Use Supabase's built-in social auth providers.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Offline Account Caching" priority="high" status="pending" id="offline-account-caching-015">
                    <comment>Cache authentication state locally to maintain logged-in experience during offline usage. Implement secure token refresh and handle authentication expiry gracefully without disrupting offline workflow.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Anonymous Usage Mode" priority="medium" status="pending" id="anonymous-usage-mode-016">
                    <comment>Allow full application functionality without account creation for privacy-conscious users. Provide clear benefits of account creation (sync, backup, advanced features) without making it mandatory for basic usage.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="User Profile &amp; Preferences Management" priority="medium" status="pending" id="user-profile-preferences-017">
                <comment>Implement user profile system that syncs preferences and settings across devices while respecting privacy. Focus on preferences that enhance productivity across devices.</comment>
                
                <node title="Cross-Device Settings Sync" priority="medium" status="pending" id="cross-device-settings-sync-018">
                    <comment>Sync user preferences through Supabase: preferred models, export formats, keyboard shortcuts, interface customizations. This creates convenience for users working across multiple Macs or future cross-platform usage.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Usage Analytics &amp; Insights" priority="low" status="pending" id="usage-analytics-insights-019">
                    <comment>Implement privacy-respectful analytics to provide users with personal insights: transcription time saved, most used features, productivity metrics. Store aggregated data in Supabase while respecting privacy preferences.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Premium Features &amp; Subscription Management" priority="high" status="pending" id="premium-features-subscription-020">
            <comment>Integrate Supabase with Stripe for subscription management while maintaining the desktop-first value proposition. Premium features should enhance core functionality rather than gate essential features.</comment>
            
            <node title="Freemium Model Architecture" priority="high" status="pending" id="freemium-model-architecture-021">
                <comment>Design freemium model that provides substantial value in free tier while creating clear upgrade incentives. Free tier should be competitive with basic transcription tools to drive adoption.</comment>
                
                <node title="Free Tier Feature Definition" priority="high" status="pending" id="free-tier-features-022">
                    <comment>Free tier includes: unlimited local transcription with Tiny/Base models, basic export formats (TXT, SRT), drag-and-drop processing, basic editing. This provides more value than most competitors' free tiers.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Premium Tier Value Proposition" priority="high" status="pending" id="premium-tier-value-prop-023">
                    <comment>Premium tier ($19.99 one-time or $4.99/month) includes: Large models, advanced export formats, cloud sync, batch processing, real-time transcription, system audio capture. Price positioning undercuts MacWhisper's premium pricing.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Enterprise/Team Features" priority="medium" status="pending" id="enterprise-team-features-024">
                    <comment>Future enterprise tier: team collaboration, shared transcript libraries, admin controls, priority support. Use Supabase Row Level Security for multi-tenant team data isolation.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Stripe Integration &amp; Payment Processing" priority="high" status="pending" id="stripe-integration-payment-025">
                <comment>Integrate Stripe through Supabase Edge Functions for secure payment processing. Support both one-time purchases and subscriptions to accommodate different user preferences.</comment>
                
                <node title="Supabase-Stripe Webhook Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="supabase-stripe-webhooks-026">
                    <comment>Set up Stripe webhooks processed through Supabase Edge Functions to handle subscription events: successful payments, failed payments, cancellations, upgrades/downgrades. Update user permissions in real-time.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="License Validation System" priority="high" status="pending" id="license-validation-system-027">
                    <comment>Implement license validation that works offline but syncs entitlements when online. Cache license status locally to prevent premium features from breaking during offline usage after valid purchase.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Payment Recovery &amp; Dunning" priority="medium" status="pending" id="payment-recovery-dunning-028">
                    <comment>Implement subscription failure recovery using Stripe's dunning management and Supabase automation. Send email notifications through Supabase for payment failures and provide in-app recovery options.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Cloud Storage &amp; File Management" priority="medium" status="pending" id="cloud-storage-file-management-029">
            <comment>Implement optional cloud storage for transcript backup and cross-device access using Supabase Storage. This is a premium feature that enhances the core offline functionality.</comment>
            
            <node title="Supabase Storage Integration" priority="medium" status="pending" id="supabase-storage-integration-030">
                <comment>Integrate Supabase Storage for encrypted transcript and audio backup. This provides data protection and cross-device access while maintaining local-first approach for privacy and performance.</comment>
                
                <node title="Encrypted Backup System" priority="medium" status="pending" id="encrypted-backup-system-031">
                    <comment>Implement client-side encryption before uploading to Supabase Storage. Users maintain full control of their data encryption keys. This addresses privacy concerns while providing cloud backup benefits.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Selective Sync Preferences" priority="medium" status="pending" id="selective-sync-preferences-032">
                    <comment>Allow users to choose what to sync: metadata only, transcripts only, or full audio+transcript backup. Provide clear storage quota information and pricing for additional storage through Stripe.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Storage Quota Management" priority="medium" status="pending" id="storage-quota-management-033">
                    <comment>Implement storage quota tracking and management UI. Show usage, provide cleanup suggestions for old files, and offer upgrade paths for additional storage. Integrate with Stripe for storage add-ons.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Real-time Features &amp; Collaboration" priority="low" status="pending" id="realtime-features-collaboration-034">
            <comment>Future enhancement: implement real-time features using Supabase Realtime for collaborative transcription editing and live transcription sharing. These are advanced features for later development phases.</comment>
            
            <node title="Real-time Transcript Collaboration" priority="low" status="pending" id="realtime-transcript-collaboration-035">
                <comment>Future feature: Allow team members to collaboratively edit transcripts in real-time using Supabase Realtime subscriptions. Include cursor presence, edit conflict resolution, and comment system for team workflows.</comment>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Live Transcription Sharing" priority="low" status="pending" id="live-transcription-sharing-036">
                <comment>Future feature: Share live transcription sessions with team members through Supabase Realtime. Useful for remote meeting participation, live captioning, and collaborative note-taking scenarios.</comment>
            </node>
        </node>
        
        <node title="Implementation Roadmap &amp; Technical Considerations" priority="high" status="pending" id="implementation-roadmap-technical-037">
            <comment>Phased implementation approach for Supabase integration that minimizes risk and allows for iterative development while maintaining focus on core transcription functionality.</comment>
            
            <node title="Phase 1: Basic Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="phase1-basic-integration-038">
                <comment>Initial Supabase integration focusing on essential features: user authentication, basic sync, and payment processing foundation. This phase enables premium features without compromising core functionality.</comment>
                
                <node title="Supabase Project Setup &amp; Configuration" priority="high" status="pending" id="supabase-project-setup-039">
                    <comment>Set up Supabase project with proper database schema, Row Level Security policies, and authentication configuration. Design schema that supports current needs while allowing for future expansion.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Authentication Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="auth-integration-implementation-040">
                    <comment>Integrate Supabase Auth into application with proper error handling, offline caching, and session management. Implement user registration/login flows that don't disrupt core application usage.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Basic Stripe Integration" priority="high" status="pending" id="basic-stripe-integration-041">
                    <comment>Implement Stripe payment processing through Supabase Edge Functions. Focus on one-time purchase flow initially, with subscription capability for future expansion. Include license validation and premium feature gating.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Phase 2: Enhanced Cloud Features" priority="medium" status="pending" id="phase2-enhanced-cloud-042">
                <comment>Advanced Supabase features that enhance user experience: cloud sync, backup, and cross-device functionality. These features differentiate VoiceFlow from competitors while maintaining offline-first approach.</comment>
                
                <node title="Transcript Sync Implementation" priority="medium" status="pending" id="transcript-sync-implementation-043">
                    <comment>Implement robust transcript metadata sync with conflict resolution. Include selective sync options and bandwidth optimization. Focus on sync reliability and user control over what syncs.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Cloud Backup System" priority="medium" status="pending" id="cloud-backup-system-044">
                    <comment>Implement encrypted backup system using Supabase Storage. Include backup scheduling, restoration capabilities, and storage management. Provide clear user control over backup frequency and content.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
            
            <node title="Technical Architecture Decisions" priority="high" status="pending" id="technical-architecture-decisions-045">
                <comment>Key technical decisions for Supabase integration that impact scalability, performance, and maintainability of the desktop application.</comment>
                
                <node title="Database Schema Design" priority="high" status="pending" id="database-schema-design-046">
                    <comment>Design Supabase database schema that mirrors local SQLite structure while optimizing for cloud sync patterns. Include proper indexing, constraints, and RLS policies for multi-tenant security.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Sync Conflict Resolution Strategy" priority="medium" status="pending" id="sync-conflict-resolution-047">
                    <comment>Implement sophisticated conflict resolution for transcript edits: detect conflicts, present merge options, and maintain edit history. Use Supabase timestamp and user tracking for conflict detection.</comment>
                </node>
                
                <node title="Error Handling &amp; Retry Logic" priority="medium" status="pending" id="error-handling-retry-048">
                    <comment>Implement robust error handling for network failures, authentication errors, and Supabase service interruptions. Include exponential backoff, queue management, and user feedback for sync status.</comment>
                </node>
            </node>
        </node>
    </node>
</project_plan>